One
of the
things
people
wonder
about
a lot
is how
I
cook.
So
the menu
today,
it's
an easy
one.
I'm
going
to go
with a
burger
and
fries.
Let's
get us
some
French
fries.
Yeah,
that's
awful.
well,
see,
So
that's
our
first
little
catastrophe
of
the day
right
here.
True.
Just
get them
all
out
over the tray.
So
I just
put
this
in the
toaster
oven
here.
We do
it
for,
like,
a
half hour,
so
we have to
plug
in the
stove
to the
stove,
the
George
Foreman
Grill,
because
this
takes
a
couple
of
minutes
to
warm
up.
The fries
are
cooking.
So
let's
see
now.
This is stupid
that
I do,
but
you have
to
sort
of
check
out.
All right.
So
let's
just
try
one
now.
Of
course.
You
know,
I'm
afraid
of
burning
myself.
You
see, I
hit
the top
of
the thing
that,
like
this,
probably
still
has a
little
ways
to go.
So
let's
make a
burger.
So
we'll
just
cook
this
for
probably
about
minutes.
And
this.
that's
where
it
goes.
It
cooks
both
sides
at
once.
It's
really
easy
to use
because
I
would
never,
you
know,
mess
with
something
with a
frying
pan.
That was
scary
to me.
What
I do
with my beer.
If
the grill
gets a
little
bit
quiet,
I'll
check
it.
I'll
just
see if
it's
in a
good spot,
maybe
move a
little
bit,
grab
the
spatula,
move
it,
and
I'll
also
touch it
to
see
how
well
it's
cut.
Because
they
say
you
touch
your
hand.
Like
this
part
here
is
rare.
Back
here
is
medium
and
out
here
as
well.
Done.
There
it is.
You're
hiding
from
me.
All right,
well,
let's
take
out
our French
fries.
Why
don't
we
just
do
that?
Of
course.
Grab a
burger
that's
unplugged
the
George
Foreman
Grill
Safety
first.
Now,
it's
not
going
to be
too
terribly
hot
because
I'm
going
to
touch
some
sort
of
help.
And
there
we go.
And
that looks
and it
didn't
land
on the
rock
nowhere
near.
So
I
threw
that.
That's
pillow
ketchup
on
here
and
there
it is.
now
that's
what I
called
delicious.
So now
we're
just
going
to
wait
while
asleep
and
then
warms
up.
See,
so
far,
not
much.
So
let's
have a
look.
You could
probably
still
touch
it.
It's
not that
warm.
No,
I won't
do
that 2
minutes
from
now.